A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Attorney General, 1988 - 1997.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Office of the Attorney General, Virginia Secretary of, Correspondence and Subject files
1988-1997.
The Library of Virginia
40174
Virginia. Office of the Attorney General. Executive Office.
4.5 cubic feet (5 boxes)
Biographical/Historical Information
The first Attorney General was commissioned in Virginia in 1642. In 1776, the state constitution adopted the office under the auspices of the General Assembly, and in in 1927 the state government reorganization act created the Department of Law with the Attorney General serving as the chief executive officer.
The Office represents the interests of the Commonwealth in civil cases in which the Commonwealth or any of its agencies or officials is named as a party, and in criminal cases on appeal to the Court of Appeals of Virginia and the Supreme Court of Virginia. In cases involving federal law, the Attorney General also represents the Commonwealth's interests. The Office also defends the constitutionality of state laws when they are challenged in court, represents consumers in utility matters before the State Corporation Commission, and collects debts owed to state agencies, hospitals and universities. Additionally, the Attorney General serves as the legal advisor to the Governor and more than 200 state agencies, boards, commissions and institutions. He renders official opinions upon the written request of the Governor, members of the General Assembly, members of the judiciary, state officials, and local constitutional officers.
James Gilmore III was elected to serve as the 38th Attorney General of Virginia from 1994 to 1997 under Governor George Allen. Gilmore resigned in June 1997 to run for the office of Governor.
Scope and Content
These records were created or collected during the administration of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994, and Governor George Allen, 1994-1998. During the Allen administration, James Gilmore served as the Attorney General (1994-1997). This series includes speeches by Gilmore and others in the office incluidng Gary Aronholt. In addition to speeches, folders include travel logistics, iteneraries, lists of attendees, newspaper clippings, invitations, and regrets.
Various arrangements. Records have been kept in their original order.
Acquisition Information
Accession 40174 was transferred by the Office of the Attorney General.
Contents List
- Speeches, 1988-1997. (Box 1-4)
  - Non-Political Speeches, 1994-1997. (Box 1-2)
    - Speech Log, 1994-1995. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Crime Solvers Banquet, 1994 Jan 22. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Commission on Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform, 1994 Feb 7. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Opening of Chesterfield County Jail Annex, 1994 Feb 7. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Known Crime Institute Press Conference, 1994 Mar 3. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Draft: Conference on Policing in the 90's, 1994 Mar 3. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Retail Merchants Association, 1994 Mar 17. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Colonial Heights Kiwanis Club, 1994 Mar 23. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County Sheriff's Banquet, 1994 Mar 26. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Commonwealth's Attorneys Meeting, 1994 Mar 27. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - T.C. Williams School of Law Event, 1994 Mar 29. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1994 Crime Bill Signing, 1994 Apr 6. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - VA YMCA Model General Assembly, 1994 Apr 15. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - VA Trial Lawyers Annual Convention, 1994 Apr 9. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform, 1994 Apr 19. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Judicial Traffic Safety Conference, 1994 Apr 26. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Sheriff's Conference, 1994 Apr 27. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Tribute to Clement E. Conger, 1994 Apr 28. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Radford University Criminal Justice Majors, 1994 Apr 29. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Judges Orientation Program, 1994 May 2. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Henrico Bar Association Dinner, 1994 May 6. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Ashland Police Banquet, 1994 May 11. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Press Conference: Special Education, 1994 May 13. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Virginia State Police Academy Graduation, 1994 May 13. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Martinsville Peace Officers, 1994 May 14. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Judicial Conference of Virginia, 1994 May 16. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Bipartisan Resolution of the Harper Litigation, 1994 May 31. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - DARE Roanoke, 1994 June 6. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - University of Richmond Law School Intern Orientation, 1994 June 14. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Parole Town Meeting - Portsmouth, 1994 June 15. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Boys/Girls State 1994 Session, 1994 June 20. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Sherrifs Assocation, 1994 July 11. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Press Conference - Signing of Harper Legislation, 1994 July 13. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Lake Gaston Water Supply Public Hearing, 1994 July 20. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Virginia Association - Chiefs of Police, 1994 Aug 15. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Speak Up Town Meeting, 1994 Aug 18. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Speak Up Town Meeting, 1994 Aug 23. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Press Conference - Parole, 1994 Aug 23. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Speak Up Town Meeting, 1994 Aug 25. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Speak Up Town Meeting, 1994 Aug 30. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Slain Officers Memorial, 1994 Sept 9. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Parole Briefing, 1994 Sept 16. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - General Assembly Kick Off, 1994 Sept 19. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - COSHA Conference, 1994 Sept 22. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Avis Rent-A-Car Reception, 1994 Oct 5. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1994 Oct 6. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Virginia Beach Chamber of Commerce, 1994 Oct 7. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation/Virginia Military Institute, 1994 Oct 12. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Virginia Beach Police Department Graduation, 1994 Oct 14. (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Virginia Wildlife Foundation, 1994 Oct 15. (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Petersburg Chamber of Commerce, 1994 Oct 25. (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - State Coorporation Commission, 1994 Oct 26. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - CNN Interview - Trigon Contract, 1994 Oct 26. (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - The Known Crime Institute, 1994 Nov 1. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Violence Prevention Conference, 1994 Nov 7. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Outside Counsel Conference, 1994 Nov 10. (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Veterans Day Ceremony, 1994 Nov 11. (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1994 Nov 14. (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Virginia Citizen's Consumer Council, 1994 Nov 16. (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Pat Murphy Show, 1994 Nov 18. (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Virginia Criminal Sentencing Commission, 1994 Dec 12. (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Retirees Press Conference, 1994 Dec 15. (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Triad Signing Ceremony, 1995 Jan 17. (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Crime Subcommittee, 1995 Jan 19. (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Commonwealth's Right of Appeal, 1995 Jan 20. (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Commonwealth's Right of Appeal Conference, 1995 Jan 20. (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - City Dialogue - Virginia Beach, 1995 Jan 23. (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Staunton/Augusta Model General Assembly, 1995 Feb 2. (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Ashland Police Department Dedication, 1995 Feb 5. (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Virginia Hospital Association, 1995 Feb 9. (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Lorton Subcommittee on DC, 1995 Mar 17. (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Governor's Committee on Juvenile Justice Reform, 1995 Mar 21. (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Commonwealth Alliance for Children, Schools, and Families, 1995 Mar 31. (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Trial Lawyers, 1995 Apr 1. (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Community Corrections Conference, 1995 Apr 4. (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Central Virginia Crime Clinic, 1995 Apr 11. (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Central Virginia Crime Victims, 1995 Apr 25. (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Victim's Rights Luncheon, 1995 Apr 27. (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Carrington Internship Virginia Beach, 1995 Apr 28. (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Israel Independence Day Vienna, 1995 Apr 30. (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Virginia Business Council, 1995 May 11. (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Juvenile Justice Reform Commission, 1995 May 16. (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Virginia State Police Memorial Service, 1995 May 17. (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Police Memorial Week, 1995 May 18. (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Peninsula Triad, 1995 May 22. (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Torch Run '95 Richmond, 1995 May 24. (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Special Olympics, 1995 June 9. (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Virginia Beach Vision Inc., 1995 June 13. (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - TRIAD Virginia Beach, 1995 June 13. (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Opening of NOVA, 1995 June 15. (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Juvenile Commission, 1995 June 15. (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Trigon News Conference, 1995 June 19. (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Factories Behind Fences, 1995 July 13. (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Juvenile Justice Reform Commission, 1995 July 25. (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Commonwealth's Attorneys, 1995 Aug 4. (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Juvenile Justice Commission, 1995 Aug 23. (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Retirees Press Conference, 1995 Sept 15. (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Intelevent '95 Berlin, 1995 Sept 28. (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Commission on Family Violence Prevention, 1995 Sept 29. (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - DARE, 1995 Oct 2. (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Triad Workshop, 1995 Oct 4. (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Juvenile Justice Commission, 1995 Oct 5. (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - James Madison University FACT, 1995 Oct 11. (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Governor's Crime Forum, 1995 Oct 12. (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Amherst Fire Department, 1995 Oct 15. (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - University of Virginia FACT, 1995 Oct 17. (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Juvenile Justice Commission, 1995 Oct 18. (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Juvenile Justice Commission, 1995 Oct 24. (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Juvenile Justice Commission, 1995 Oct 26. (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Virginia NAACP State Conference, 1995 Nov 4. (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Rabin Memorial, 1995 Nov 6. (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Cannon Virginia 15th Anniversary, 1995 Nov 15. (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Reebok News Conference, 1995 Dec 4. (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1995 Dec 6. (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Trigon Press Conference, 1995 Dec 7. (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Virginia Israel Partnership, 1995 Dec 7. (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Sidney O. Dewberry Collection, 1995 Dec 11. (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - March of Dimes Board of Directors Reception, 1995 Dec 12. (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Juvenile Justice Commission Final, 1995 Dec 20. (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Family Violence Prevention, 1995 Dec 19. (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Speech Log, 1996-1997. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Shore Bussinessmen, 1996 Jan 4. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Union University Community Learning Week, 1996 Jan 12. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Foster Grandparents, 1996 Jan 19. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Unsung Virginians Award - Electric Co-Ops Association, 1996 Jan 22. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - National Federation Independent Business, 1996 Jan 24. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ITSVA Conference, 1996 Jan 29. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - AARP Legislative Day, 1996 Jan 30. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - News Conference: Juvenile Justice (Governor Jones), 1996 Jan 31. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Senate Courts of Justice, 1996 Jan 31. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Strong Men and Women, 1996 Feb 1. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Henrico Triad Signing, 1996 Feb 6. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Richmond Triad, 1996 Feb 12. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Sha'arei Torah 2nd Annual Dinner, 1996 Feb 12. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Community Learning Week, 1996 Feb 23. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Hate Crimes News Conference, 1996 Feb 26. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Family and Children's Trust Fund (FACT) Gala, 1996 Feb 28. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Pledge of Allegiance Bill Signing, 1996 Mar 7. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Portsmouth Triad, 1996 Mar 20. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 10th Amendment Testimony, 1996 Mar 21. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Council on Indians, 1996 Mar 22. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Mother's Against Drunk Driving (MADD), 1996 Mar 26. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Coalition on Aging, 1996 Apr 12. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Driving Under the Influence Roadblock, 1996 Apr 12. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Commonwealth Attorneys, 1996 Apr 14. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Tower Club Meeting, 1996 Apr 16. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Rotary District Conference, 1996 Apr 19. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Pro Bono Awards Ceremony, 1996 May 7. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Attorney General's High Tech Council, 1996 May 14. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Hanover Business Coalition on Drugs and Alcohol in the Workplace, 1996 May 16. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Special Olympics, 1996 May 29. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Lorton Press Conference, 1996 June 13. (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Attorney General's Seniors Conference, 1996 June 17. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Boys and Girls State, 1996 June 18. (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Family Violence Conference, 1996 June 20. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Harrisonburg and Rockingham Speech, 1996 June 26. (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Attorney General's Summit, 1996 July 2. (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Virginia Bar Association Summer Meeting, 1996 July 19. (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Lynchburg Town Meeting, 1996 July 23. (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Youth Alcohol and Drug Abuse Prevention Project Conference, 1996 July 23. (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Environmental Stewardship, 1996 July 30. (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Bass Weigh-In at the Hideway, 1996 Aug 3. (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Safe Schools, 1996 Aug 5. (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - News Conference, 1996 Sept 4. (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Opening Remarks - Conference, 1996 Sept 4. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Virginia Sheriff's Association, 1996 Sept 10. (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Crime Forum, 1996 Oct 15. (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Victim's Rights: William and Mary, 1996 Oct 17. (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Virginia School Superintendents, 1996 Oct 17. (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce, 1996 Oct 18. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - World Trade Conference, 1996 Oct 21. (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Virginia Auto Dealers, 1996 Oct 24. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Urban Forests, 1996 Oct 30. (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Virginia NAACP State Conference, 1996 Nov 2. (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - West End Rotary, 1996 Nov 6. (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - University of Richmond Business School: New Century Scholars, 1996 Nov 7. (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - McGuire Medical Center, 1996 Nov 8. (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Tobacco News Conference, 1996 Nov 13. (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Economic Leadership Conference, 1996 Dec 5. (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Convention, 1996 Dec 5. (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Attorney General's Calls for Secure Literacy Fund, 1996 Dec 16. (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Environmental Stewardship Commission, 1996 Dec 18. (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Virginia for Improved Education, 1997 Jan 9. (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - National Federation of Independent Business, 1997 Jan 15. (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Virginia Jewish Lobby Day, 1997 Jan 16. (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Association of General Contractors, 1997 Jan 17. (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Virginia Association of Realtors, 1997 Jan 17. (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Mothers Against Drunk Driving, 1997 Jan 18. (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - NAACP, 1997 Jan 19. (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Virginia Association of College and University Presidents, 1997 Jan 21. (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Community College Day, 1997 Jan 23. (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Tet '68 Reunion, 1997 Feb 1. (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Nova Technology, 1997 Feb 4. (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Fairfax Chamber of Business Crime, 1997 Feb 4. (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Attorney General's Consumer Fraud Exhibit, 1997 Feb 28. (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Weed and Seed, 1997 Mar 6. (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1997 Mar 24. (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Westmoreland Coal News Conference, 1997 Mar 26. (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Law Enforcement Memorial Service - Virginia Beach Fraternal Order of Police, 1997 May 12. (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Office of Attorney General Farewell, 1997 June 6. (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1997 July 30. (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Political Speeches, 1992-1997. (Box 2-3)
    - Political Speech Log, 1994-1995. (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Announcement Speech, 1992 Nov 11. (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Virginia State Bar, 1993 June 19. (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - FCA Remarks, 1993 July 9. (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Remarks, 1993 Nov 5. (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Remarks Introducing Governer Elect Allen, 1993 Dec 13. (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Attorney General's Dinner, 1994 Jan 14. (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Crime Solvers Banquet, 1994 Jan 22. (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Virginia Dental Association, 1994 Jan 29. (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Report on Crime to the General Assembly, 1994 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Sixth District Dinner, 1994 Feb 4. (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Virginia Federation of Republican Women 1994 Legislative Day, 1994 Feb 16. (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Republican Advance, 1994 Feb 19. (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Virginia Institute of Political Leadership, 1994 Mar 5. (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - The Tusk and Trunk Club, 1994 Mar 18. (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Jewish Community Federation, 1994 Apr 7. (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Friends of Bill Bolling, 1994 Apr 10. (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Friends of Brian Campbell, 1994 Apr 13. (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Roanoke Press Conference, 1994 Apr 22. (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Roanoke GOP, 1994 Apr 22. (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Republican Leadership Dinner, 1994 Apr 23. (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Congressman Thomas J. Bliley Roast, 1994 Apr 25. (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Metropolitan Lodge Dinner, 1994 May 12. (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Fifth District Convention, 1994 May 14. (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Sixth District Convention, 1994 May 14. (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Goodlatte Fundraiser, 1994 May 13. (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Richmond Auto Dealers, 1994 May 17. (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Eigth District Convention, 1994 May 21. (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Eleventh District Convention, 1994 May 21. (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - George Mason Law School, 1994 May 21. (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - National Policy Forum, 1994 May 25. (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Beecher Family, 1994 May 31. (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Alexandria Town Meeting, 1994 June 2. (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - GOP Convention, 1994 June 4. (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - GOP Unity Breakfast, 1994 June 5. (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Shenandoah Club Business Luncheon, 1994 June 6. (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - NRA, 1994 June 11. (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - George Landrith Fundraiser, 1994 June 16. (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Governor's Forum, 1994 June 16. (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Bob McDonnel Fundraiser, 1994 July 11. (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Virginia Bar Association Meeting, 1994 July 14. (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Hazel-Thomas Leadership Breakfast, 1994 July 19. (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Friends of Tom Davis, 1994 July 30. (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Commonwealth Attorneys Association, 1994 Aug 4. (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Speak Up Town Meeting, 1994 Aug 18. (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Steve Fast Fundraiser, 1994 Aug 20. (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Parole Press Conference, 1994 Aug 24. (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Virginia Beach Downtown Republican Club, 1994 Aug 26. (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Northern Virginia Media, 1994 Aug 30. (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Labor Day Events, 1994 Sept 5. (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Herrity and Pennino Building Dedication, 1994 Sept 12. (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Fairfax County Event, 1994 Sept 17. (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Ollide North Fundraiser, 1994 Sept 23. (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Judicial Luncheon, 1994 Sept 30. (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Regent University, 1994 Oct 1. (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - VALECO, 1994 Oct 3. (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Chesapeake GOP Awards Dinner, 1994 Oct 13. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - George Sweet Fundraiser, 1994 Oct 13. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Bliley Breakfast, 1994 Oct 17. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Governor Allen Roast, 1994 Oct 18. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - NOVA GOP Business Forum, 1994 Oct 21. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Dan Ross Event, 1994 Oct 21. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - North News Conference, 1994 Oct 26. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Eastern Armed Robbery Conference, 1994 Oct 27. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Ollie North Rally, 1994 Oct 30. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Hazel Breakfast, 1994 Nov 10. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Greater McLean GOP Women's Club, 1994 Nov 10. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Federalism Press Conference, 1994 Nov 14. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Internal Auditors Banquet, 1994 Nov 14. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Voter Registrars' Association, 1994 Dec 1. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Friday Club, 1994 Dec 16. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - RPV Volunteer Awards, 1994 Dec 19. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Berger Press Conference, 1994 Dec 21. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Republican Advance, 1995 Jan 14. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Virginia State FOP, 1995 Jan 22. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Victims' Rights Rally, 1995 Jan 24. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Virginia FOP Law Enforcement Appreciation Day, 1995 Jan 25. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Prayer Breakfast, 1885 Jan 26. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Health Care Association, 1995 Feb 1. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Elaine McConnell Fundraiser, 1995 Feb 4. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - College GOP Convention, 1995 Feb 4. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Nurses Association, 1995 Feb 6. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - VFRW Legislative Day, 1995 Feb 8. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1995 Feb 18. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Sons of the Revolution, 1995 Feb 22. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Northern Virginia Auto Dealers, 1995 Feb 24. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Attorney General's Dinner, 1995 Mar 4. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Williamsburg, 1995 Mar 16. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Williamsburg, 1995 Mar 19. (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Richmond/Norfolk Press Conference, 1995 Mar 29. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Emergency Shelter Roast, 1995 Apr 4. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Republican National Lawyers Association, 1995 Apr 6. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - St. Paul's College, 1995 Apr 12. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Commonwealth Gala, 1995 Apr 21. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - First Thursday Club, 1995 May 4. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - VFRW, 1995 May 7. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Governor's Dinner, 1995 May 16. (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Leadership Awards, 1995 June 16. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - 7th District Fundraiser, 1995 July 15. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - WRC Radio Interview, 1995 July 16. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Frank Wolf and Tom Davis Tribute, 1995 July 17. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Virginia Sheriff's Association, 1995 July 18. (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - NOVA Luncheon, 1995 July 18. (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Faye Palmer Fundraiser, 1995 July 25. (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Masonic Lodge, 1995 July 25. (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Virginia Bar Association, 1995 July 28. (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Trixie Averill, 1995 Aug 22. (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Marty Williams, 1995 Aug 30. (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Henrico Business Council, 1995 Sept 14. (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Anthony Moore Campaign, 1995 Sept 15. (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Contract with Virginia, 1995 Sept 20. (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Republican Dinner, 1995 Oct 3. (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - NOVA Press Conference, 1995 Oct 26. (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - This Week in Richmond Interview, 1995 Nov 2. (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Radio Interview, 1995 Nov 5. (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Wayne LaPierre Interview, 1995 Nov 5. (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Parliament Club, 1995 Nov 16. (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Delegate Jay O'Brien Birthday, 1995 Dec 11. (Box 3, Folder 63)